now it's time to play thug life or hug
life if you don't know unexpected thug
life then you don't know sh it's a
classic internet meme that exposes
seemingly innocent little kids uh for
the hard ass mother suckers that they
really are this clip sums up this is
this is really what Thug life's all
about say hello to the camera hello
[Applause]
motherucker
I never I never wanted to be a father
until right now oh that is good
comedians I'm going to show you what
still is something adorable and for 250
points I want you to tell me if they are
cute little hugs or cute little thugs
all right answer hugs or thugs first one
this goddamn Ginger thug life or hug
life Bobcat I'm going to go uh thug life
all right let's
see my shut the
up I got to give Little Richie
Cunningham credit for uh first saying to
the front of the bus if you didn't hear
the he goes excuse my language shut the
up it's very polite can't play Both
Sides myin yeah oh my God there's two of
you all right next one how about these
adorable
children
Jonah hug life I think you may be
surprised
you I
mean I mean as
soon as soon as he started
muttering the baby should have been
taken away that's like any woman knows
that as soon as a guy's muttering on the
subway you switch cars you know yeah I
did not expect that so fued
up they're fine probably yeah I feel bad
just the parent that films it and just
goes Thug Life meme yeah
yeah don't worry we'll make another one
that was that was take
[Laughter]
four
yeah there was just a whole bucket of
babies they were going through right
there bucket of babies bucket of babies
will be all right next one what about
this math whiz thug life or hug life yes
Julie I'm going to hope hug life let's
see I love how people are telling me I'm
like two n years old I'm 11 so shut the
[Music]
up next one this little selfie thug life
or hug life Jonah uh thug life cuz he's
he looks like a young Eminem yeah
points kids are you ready for Modern
Warfare
3 well you're not old enough to play it
so get
the he almost almost went hug he almost
went hug I don't know I think that's hug
life he was on the border of hug and
then went straight into Thug shut
the which why are you Whispering so your
parents don't hear when you're going to
put it on the
internet last one this one may surprise
you thug life or hug life Julie say thug
life because they've all been Thug Life
okay let's see what did you learn in
school
today he learned not to go pee peee in
your pants huh Yay good job Rock
[Applause]
car